The emperor seems to be feeling
皇天好像有感应
should be in there
应该就在里面
I found it
我找到了
Why can't this door be opened
这门怎么打不开
is it a trap?
是陷阱吗
It's not like a trap
好像不是陷阱
why is this
为什么会这样
I do not know either
我也不知道
It should be blocked in there
里面应该被堵上了
I come
我来
Your Highness, let me come
殿下 我来吧
It's really weird
这地道确实古怪
how did you come
你怎么来
Xijing starts from Jiuyi Mountain
西京 从到这九屹山开始
You stand in front of me everywhere
你就处处挡在我前面
look at you
你看你这一副
Ready to die anytime
随时准备赴死的样子
If you do this again
你要是再这样的话
I'm so pissed
我可真要生气了
I do not want
我不想
I don't want to see anyone leave
不想再看到任何人离开了
Your Highness
殿下
All right
好了
I'll come
还是我来吧
anyway
再怎么说
There are also my ancestors lying here
这里面躺着的也是我的祖先
There is no reason to bless the children and grandchildren.
这断无不保佑子孙的道理吧
Nasheng
那笙
come over
过来
i'm still angry
我还生气呢
Nasheng
那笙
All right
好了
I just couldn't control my emotions
刚刚是我没控制好情绪
sorry
对不起啊
I know
我知道
Prince brother
太子哥哥
Thousands of children are important to you
对于你来说万千子民固然重要
but in my heart
但在我心里
I only have sister Bai Ying in my heart
我心里只有白璎姐姐一个
so
所以啊
we have to hurry up
我们要抓紧时间
Maybe there's still a chance to save them
说不准 还有机会可以救他们
You only have one sister Bai Ying
你只有一个白璎姐姐
And me
我呢
She is the only white king
也只有她这一个白王
I won't watch her die
我不会眼睁睁地看着她死的
so
所以
so i know
所以 我知道
Don't make a fuss at this time
这时候不能闹
good Nasheng
好那笙
you let go
你们先让一让
everyone remembered
大家记住了
There are many organs in this mausoleum
这陵墓里机关重重
be careful
务必要小心
Is there water on this?
这上面是水吗
here under weak water
此处在弱水之下
It must be weak water.
那应该就是弱水了吧
Then why doesn't the water flow down?
那这水为什么不会流下来啊
upper bound
上方设有结界
Otherwise, the mausoleum will not be built under weak water.
否则也不会在弱水下建寝陵
from beads
离珠
Prince
太子
follow carefully
跟去看看 小心
Yes
是
what happened to the bead
离珠到底怎么回事
leave her alone
先别管她了
Find the seal
找封印要紧
Nasheng
那笙
Prince brother
太子哥哥
Nasheng Nasheng
那笙 那笙
Nasheng
那笙
The mountains and rivers are forever silent
山河永寂
This is the calligraphy of the King of Stars, right?
这是星尊王的墨宝吧
Nasheng
那笙
here in Xijing
西京 这边
Nasheng Nasheng
那笙 那笙
just passed out
只是晕过去了
Nasheng
那笙
wake up
快醒醒
wake up Nasheng
快醒醒 那笙
Nasheng
那笙
let go of me let go of my sheng
放开我 放开我 那笙
It's us
是我们
The prince's brother just had someone
太子哥哥 刚刚有个人
Someone kidnapped me
有个人把我掳走了
He's going to steal my ring
他还要抢我的戒指
ok it's alright
好了 没事了
Why do you want to steal your ring
为什么要抢你戒指
I don't know
我也不知道 就
He just dragged my hand
他刚才就拖着我的手
Then I fainted
然后我就晕过去了
stand up
起来
Where is this
这是哪儿啊
King Star's Mausoleum
星尊王的陵墓
what is this
那这是什么呀
Star King's Coffin
星尊王的棺椁
yes yes yes
对 对对对
right here right here
就是这儿 就是这儿
He just dragged me here
就是他刚把我拖到这儿的
And the closer to the emperor, the brighter
而且越靠近皇天就越亮
Why doesn't the emperor light up?
皇天怎么不亮了
what's the situation
什么情况
Nasheng, come here
那笙 你过来
hand
手
His Royal Highness Nasheng
殿下 那笙
Be careful
小心
This coffin has been moved
这棺椁被人动过了
Someone opened it first
有人先打开过了
The Mausoleum of the King of Stars
这星尊王的陵墓
How could anyone move this coffin
怎么会有人动过这棺椁
open to take a look
打开看看
Nasheng Nasheng
那笙 那笙
Your Highness, what did you see?
殿下 你看到了什么
my descendants
我的后裔
when you open the coffin
当你打开这棺椁
life and death overlap
生与死重叠
Start and end overlap
起点与终点重叠
everything comes round
一切终入轮回
like mirror reflection
如镜像倒影
Your Highness, how are you?
殿下 你还好吗
what memory is this
这是什么记忆
Why is the King of Stars my face?
星尊王为何是我的脸
Queen Baiwei and Aying are exactly the same
白薇王后和阿璎也是一模一样
Did someone kill Bai Wei?
是有人杀了白薇吗
Your Highness
殿下
what did you see
你到底看到了什么
wife brother
太 太子哥哥
don't scare me, what's wrong with you
你别吓我啊 你怎么了
I just saw the King of Stars
我刚刚看到星尊王他
how so
怎么会这样
There is no hexagram here
这里面没有六合封印
There is no skeleton of the King of Stars
也没有星尊王的骸骨
This is an empty coffin
这是个空棺
Who was the one who just took me?
那刚刚抓走我的人是谁啊
who is so bold
谁这么大胆
Is it a treasure thief
难道是盗宝者
impossible
不可能
If it is really according to what Li Zhu said
如果真的按照离珠所言
Then all these years
那么这些年
No one can come here from the pavilion of life and death
就没有人能够从生死亭到这里来
only one possibility
只有一个可能
it's the guy in here
是这里面的人
Who was the one who caught me just now?
那刚才抓我的人是谁啊
ghost is ghost
是鬼 是鬼
from the moment we entered
从我们一进这里来
Someone took the opportunity to kidnap Na Sheng
就有人趁机掳走那笙
Then use Na Sheng's ring to open the coffin
然后用那笙的戒指打开这棺椁
Always feel something is wrong
总觉得有什么不对
The design of the coffin
这个棺椁的设计
as if waiting for someone to open it
就好像等着谁来打开
who is waiting
究竟是谁在等着
who will open
由谁来打开
Looks like there are other people in this tomb
看来这个陵墓里面还有其他人
Their purpose is also the Six Harmony Seal
他们的目的也是六合封印
Qingyuan
青塬
go see
去看看
Nasheng, recite an invisibility spell
那笙 你念个隐身咒
Come out when it's safe
等安全了再出来
All right, you have to be careful
行 那你们千万要小心啊
good
好
from beads
离珠
don't bother
不要费力了
witch
妖女
He even stepped into the mausoleum of King Xingzun
竟然还踏进了星尊王的陵墓
You should have been executed
当年就该将你处死
How could King Jiuyi let a guy like you
九屹王怎么会让你这种家伙
survived
活下来了
This is the mausoleum of King Xingzun
这里是星尊王的陵墓
You dare to rush
你们也敢乱闯
I want to ask who you are
我倒要问问你是谁
he is the one
他就是
The guardian of the mausoleum of our Qing clan
我们青氏一族的守陵人
But why are you alone here?
不过怎么只有你一个人在这儿
For hundreds of years
这百年来
Mausoleum keeper escaped to death
守陵人逃的逃 死的死
It's long gone
早就所剩无几了
As long as my old bones are
只要我这把老骨头在
You don't even think about trespassing
你们就休想擅闯
This is Prince Kong Sang
这位是空桑太子
Kongsang died a hundred years ago
百年前 空桑早就亡了
What are you talking about, prince?
还提什么太子 你
Since it's dead
既然已经亡了
Why are you still holding onto these tablets?
你又为何 还守着这些牌位
We are for the king
我们是为王而守的
Is it the king of Kongsang or the king of Qing?
是空桑的王还是青氏的王
Even the Qing clan is for Kongsang
就算是青氏也是为了空桑
Whether you recognize me or not
你认我也好 不认也罢
Our purpose is the same
我们的目的都是一样的
Where is the seal of six
六合封印在何处
Did you move the skeleton of the King of Stars?
星尊王的骸骨是你动的吗
skeleton
骸骨
There is no king's skeleton from beginning to end
自始至终就没有王的骸骨
how is this possible
怎么可能
if there are no bones
若是没有骸骨
Where is the real body of the King of Stars?
那星尊王的真身在何处呢
Be careful
小心
don't chase
不要追
King Xingzun's Mausoleum is like an ant's nest
星尊王陵墓犹如蚁穴
if there is no map
如果没有地图
Even if the bead leads the way
就算离珠带路
also get lost
也会迷失其中
He's trying to lure us into the dark on purpose
他是想要将我们故意引入黑暗中
who are you
你们又是何人
There seems to be someone in there
里面好像有什么人
everyone be careful
大家小心
A Ying Su G
阿璎 苏摹
you
你们
still alive
还活着
how so
怎么会这样
before in the pavilion of life and death
之前在生死亭
The Heaven-defying Sword can split the water mist
辟天剑可以劈开水雾
I think it must be able to split weak water
我想它一定可以劈开弱水
But
可是
Let's meet you all right now
我们还是赶紧跟大家会合吧
Su G
苏摹
thank you
谢谢你啊
what to thank
有什么好谢的
don't say it again
以后不要再说
I'm sorry, thank you, etc.
对不起 谢谢之类的话了
After leaving Jiuyi
离开九屹之后
I have something to say to you
我有话想要对你说
Ok, I will wait for you
好 我等你
We found there was light ahead
我们发现前面有光
come down this passage
顺着这个通道过来
just saw him
就看到了他
Sister Bai Ying
白璎姐姐
Great, great, you're still alive
太好了太好了 你们还活着
You're not allowed to scare me like this again
你以后都不许再这样吓我了
so worry about you
好 让你担心了
Don't worry, I'm fine
放心吧 我没有事
it's fine
没事就好
Worried Your Highness
让殿下担心了
Stay safe, Su G
别来无恙啊 苏摹
A Ying
阿璎
It's Qing Wangchen
是青王辰
Who is that person?
人呢 那个人到底是谁
Qing Wangchen
青王辰
Didn't he die a hundred years ago?
百年前他不是死了吗
It seems that in the past hundred years
看来这百年里
he's been living here
他一直活在这儿
No news of him in a hundred years
百年里没有他的消息
It turned out that he was living in this mausoleum
原来他是苟活在这陵墓里
Your Highness, is that the Seal of Six Harmonies?
殿下 那是六合封印吗
Why does the emperor ring not respond?
为何皇天戒指没有反应
go fast
快走
How are you
你怎么样
You are hurt
你受伤了
come out of the way
不碍事 来
what's the matter, ice cube brother
怎么回事 冰块哥哥
what's the matter
什么情况啊
the seal just now
刚刚那个封印
That's not a seal
那不是封印
Because Na Sheng's Emperor's Ring did not light up
因为那笙的皇天戒指并没有亮
That means
那也就是说
This is a trap set up by Qingchen
这是青辰布置的陷阱
Where is that really sealed?
那真的封印在哪儿
must be on him
一定在他身上
Be careful
小心
it's not safe here
这儿不安全
Come with me first
大家先跟我走吧
quick
快
walk, walk, walk
走 走 快走
I'll block the door and get out this way
我来挡着门 快从这边走
hurry up
快 快
Uncle Xijing
西京大叔
Sister Bai Ying Sister Bai Ying
白璎姐姐 白璎姐姐
go fast
快走
My perching star lamp perching star lamp
我的栖星灯 栖星灯
The star lamp is still inside
栖星灯还在里面
I come
我来
go fast
走 快走
We're blocked here too
我们这里也被堵住了
what should we do
咱们该怎么办
I've experienced it once before.
之前生死亭都经历过一次了
This time it's a dead end
这次还是死胡同
How about it
怎么样
Thank you Haihuang for helping me take out the perched star lamp
多谢海皇帮我取出栖星灯
He was injured by the explosion just now
刚刚的爆炸让他受伤了
also triggered a backlash
还触发了反噬
My trick is to catch turtles in the urn
我这招瓮中捉鳖
how are you guys
如何呀 几位
what sound
什么声音啊
Blue dragon
青辰
This tomb is about to collapse
这陵墓马上就要塌了
you all can't live
你们全都活不了
will die here
都要死在这里
Right now
眼下看来
The organs of the entire underground palace
整个地宫的机关
It was all opened by that Qingchen
都被那青辰给开启了
it's irreversible
已经不可逆了
what would happen
那会怎么样
To prevent treasure thieves
为了防止盗宝者
The agency will close all exits
机关会封闭所有的出口
no one can get out
任谁都出不去
Qingchen's fake seal
青辰的那个假封印
Broke one of the foundations of the underground palace
把地宫的一处根基给炸断了
So I'm afraid the whole underground palace will collapse
所以恐怕整个地宫都会塌陷
from beads
离珠
you brought us here
你把我们引到这里来
Impossible to leave behind
不可能不留后路的
export
出口呢
Let me try
我试试
How can it be so impossible?
怎么会这样 不可能啊
He clearly told me so
他分明是这样告诉我的
who told you that
谁这样跟你说的
Qingjun
青骏
he told me
他跟我说
Emergency moment
危急时刻
You can stick the star lamp on the stone pillar
可以把栖星灯卡在石柱上
And use magic to copy the character of silence
并以法术临摹寂字
In this way, the cave will open a secret passage.
这样天洞就会打开一个密道
can escape
可以逃出
Qing Jun was never found
青骏从来就没有找到过
How to enter the Mausoleum of King Xingzun
进入星尊王陵墓的方法
How could he know how to get out?
他又怎么会知道如何出去呢
That's right
没错
From the beginning
从一开始
He just wanted to bury you here
他就想将你一起埋在这儿
Lizhu why did you lead us here
离珠 你为什么把我们引到这里
What kind of contract do you have with Qingjun?
你跟青骏到底有什么样的契约
from beads
离珠
tell everyone
你告诉大家吧
turn off the lights
把灯熄了吧
you told us before
你之前告诉我们
It's your own choice
这是你自己的选择
So I didn't pierce you
所以我没有戳穿你
But so far
可是事到如今
Do you still believe in Qingjun?
你还要相信青骏吗
Xuan Huang Sutra says
玄黄经上说
This mausoleum has a very strong magic enchantment
这陵墓中设有极强的法术结界
Only the star-dwelling lamp of the King of Stars
只有星尊王的栖星灯
to light up here
才能将这里照亮
And this star lamp
而这栖星灯
need special people
也需要特殊的人
to light up
才能点亮
yes yes yes
对对对对
That light couldn't be lit in my hand before
那个灯之前在我手里点亮不了
Lights up in her hands
在她手里就点亮了
This star lamp burns
这栖星灯燃烧的
is the life of the lamp bearer
是持灯者的生命
so scary
这么恐怖
The longer you keep the lights on
你点灯越久
Life will be consumed faster
生命便消耗得越快
You've been holding the light for so long
你已经持灯这么久了
Even if you complete the task that Qingjun gave you
就算是完成青骏交给你的任务
The star lights go out
这栖星灯灭
you will still die
你照样会死
from beads
离珠
what exactly is it
到底是什么
make you willing to give your life
让你愿意付出生命
from beads
离珠
you really want for this lamp
你真的想要为了这盏灯
give your life?
付出自己的生命吗
I co-starred with Qing Jun in this play
我和青骏合演了这出戏
It's because Qingjun once promised me
就是因为青骏他曾经答应过我
As long as I light the perched star lamp
只要我点亮栖星灯
lead you to the tunnel
把你们引到地道来
And kill that Qingchen
且杀了那青辰
He will set my family free
他就会放我家人自由
I clearly made a blood pact with him
我明明跟他定了血契
But he
可是他竟然
He has been from the beginning
他竟然从一开始
Just planned to bury me here
就已经算计好要把我埋葬在这里
Why
为什么
I tried my best
我拼尽了全力
All I want is freedom
想要的只是自由啊
Even if only one day to live
哪怕只有一天可以活着
I want to go back to that sea too
我也想回到那片海
Sister Lizhu Sister Lizhu
离珠姐姐 离珠姐姐
Sorry
对不起
Before
之前
I made you angry before
之前是我让你生气了
I can help you destroy this lamp
我可以帮你毁了这盏灯
I can also kill Qingjun
我也可以杀了青骏
save your family
救回你的家人
Because you have Quanxian's blood on you
因为你身上流着泉先的血
I have to take you home
我就一定要带你回家
from beads
离珠
you believe me
你是信我
still believe in yourself
还是信你自己
Still believe that Qingjun
还是信那青骏
you decide
你自己决定吧
I believe you
我信你
Neptune
海皇
Xie Haihuang
谢海皇
Major General
少将军
The stone that seals the door has been moved in.
封门的石料都已经搬进来了
hold on
再等等
I don't know that you brought me here
不知阁下把我引到这儿来
what to say
是要说什么
Major General Yu Huan please
请羽幻少将军
meet someone with me
跟我去见一个人
who to see
见谁
The real Jiuyi King
真正的九屹王
Meet King Jiuyi
拜见九屹王
Yu Huan has seen King Jiuyi
羽幻见过九屹王
The Major General really lives up to his reputation
少将军果然名不虚传哪
I can actually see that the medicine pill is for me
竟然能看出丹药是给我的
When I bring the elixir
我将丹药带来时
Qingjun doesn't care
青骏并不在意
I know
我便知
People who really need medicine
真正急需丹药之人
not him
不是他
and
而且
He has changed about Jiuyi Mountain
他对九屹山有变之事
don't know
也不甚了解
The Qing's soldiers didn't protect him either.
这青氏的士兵也并未保护他
I will conclude
我便断定
The real King Jiuyi is someone else
真正的九屹王另有其人
Lord Prey sent you to come alone
鸷者大人派你孤身前来
For the arrest of Su G Zhenlan
对于捉拿苏摹 真岚
follow-up plans
可有后续计划
In my opinion, it is better to count
依我看 不如将计就计
lead them into the mausoleum
把他们引入陵墓中
Why
为什么
The Mausoleum of King Xingzun
这星尊王陵墓
hard to get in
想进去难
It's harder to figure out
可想出来 更难
Then let Miaozhu stay in the tomb for me
那就让庙祝替我留在墓中
bait them
引他们上钩
Yiyu Fantasy
依羽幻看
You should do the bait yourself
应该您亲自做诱饵
If it were someone else
如若换作他人的话
Presumably this Su G
想必这个苏摹
It shouldn't be that easy to get hooked on.
应该没有那么容易上钩吧
If Qing Wang is worried
青王若是担心
Can hold the seal of Liuhe
可将六合封印傍身
There are six seals in
有六合封印在
Su G dare not do anything to you
苏摹不敢对你怎么样
The six seals
这六合封印
Still sealed in the coffin
还封存于棺椁之中
Requires Emperor Ring
需要皇天戒指
to open the coffin
才能开棺取出
Yu Huan has seen King Jiuyi
羽幻见过九屹王
King Jiuyi King Jiuyi
九屹王 九屹王
As the Major General expected
如少将军所料
Kill two birds with one stone
一箭双雕
Catching turtle in urn
瓮中捉鳖
Everyone is ambushing on this rocky cliff
所有人 在此石崖埋伏
Yes
是
wait
慢着
who are you
你是何人
I am Major General Cang Liu
我乃沧流少将军
Fei Lian
飞廉
less bullshit
少胡说
How dare you pretend to be me
你敢冒充我
Lord Shilang's Jialing plaque is here
师朗大人嘉陵牌在此
who dares
谁敢造次
it is true
是真的
Then the lieutenant
那么这位少将军
can you take a look at your token
可否看一下您的令牌
You are the girl who throws her arms around you
你是那个投怀送抱的姑娘
you are the girl
你才是姑娘呢
How dare you be so rude to this general
敢对本将军如此无礼
take it for me
给我拿下
what are you doing
愣着干什么
Who is this listening to?
这到底听谁的
you little thief
你这个小贼
should take you down
应该把你拿下才是
squad leader
小队长
Shall we go help?
我们要不要去帮帮忙
what help
帮什么忙
do you know who they are
你知道他们谁是谁吗
Why have you tried so many ways?
为什么试了这么多办法
Still can't break the barrier
还是破不了结界
Weak above, soul below
上为弱水下为魂
The boundary of this
这当中的结界
the ancestors of Kongsang
是空桑历代先祖
Continued with the blessing of mana
不断以法力加持而成
unbreakable
牢不可破
Otherwise, the weak water will break through the barrier and go down
否则弱水破结界而下
It will damage the coffin of the King of Stars
则会损坏星尊王的棺椁
and the thrones of the kings
和各王的牌位
what to do then
那怎么办啊
We're not going to die here are we?
我们不会要死在这儿吧
The emperor didn't use the lightsaber either.
皇天也没用 光剑也没用
Let's fight like this
我们这样打下去
when is it over
什么时候是个完
Why don't we go our separate ways
不如我们各走各的
You go to Yuhuan
你去找羽幻
How about I go to the young master
我去找少主 怎么样
Be careful
小心
thanks
谢谢
not shaking
地不抖了
Will the mountain not collapse?
是不是山不会塌了
How is this going
这是怎么回事
what what
什么 什么东西
What's this
这是什么
wait
且慢
It's dodder, don't hurt her
是菟萝 别伤害她
Dodder
菟萝
This is dodder
这就是菟萝啊
she is a shark
她是鲛人
Saved me and Su G in the foggy forest
在迷雾森林里面救过我跟苏摹
See Neptune, I'm late
参见海皇 我来迟了
how are you hurt
你怎么受伤了
Farewell to the foggy forest
迷雾森林一别
I was ordered to find Bai Lin
我奉命去寻找白麟
I saw her and that major general in Cang Liu
我看见她和沧流的那个少将军
conspiring together
一起密谋着什么
I caught her after she left alone
她独自离开后我抓了她
But after she tore up all the vines
可是她撕烂了所有藤蔓之后
Ran away
逃走了
missing
下落不明
you say liner
你说麟儿
how could she be so cruel
她怎么会如此残忍
why should i lie to you
我又何必骗你呢
dodder girl
菟萝姑娘
You can go to this underground palace
你既能到这地宫里
Can you show us a way out
可否为我们指一条出路
It's you
是你
dodder girl
菟萝姑娘
what's wrong with you
你 你怎么了
don't you remember me
你不记得我了吗
we have seen
我们见过
I'm confused
是我糊涂了
you can't be him
你不可能是他
but you
但是 你
You look so alike
你们长得实在太像了
me we
我 我们
what are we like
我们像什么
The world is but fate
尘世不过宿命啊
do you want it
你要不要紧
fine
没事
A dirty thing got in there
竟然混进来一个脏东西
Lizhu, you are so damned
离珠 你真该死
get out of the way what are you gonna do
让开 你要做什么
it's not your turn to speak
轮不到你说话
Neptune
海皇
She's the one who tricked everyone into coming here
就是她把所有人骗到这儿来的
don't blame her
不怪她
She was also deceived by Qing Jun
她也是被青骏所骗
I'll open a channel in a while
一会儿我打开一条通道
Do you know the way down the mountain?
你知道下山的路吧
if you dare to betray
如果你敢背叛
I will take your father and brother to the misty forest
我定把你的父兄抓到迷雾森林
make them the most miserable monsters
让他们沦为最可怜的怪物
Neptune
海皇
I will open a passage to the back mountain for a while
我一会儿撑开一条通道到后山
In this way, everyone can get out of Jiuyi Mountain.
这样大家就可以出九屹山了
good
好
Once the agency is opened
机关一旦开启
won't close
就不会闭合
Su G is not so easy to die
苏摹没那么容易死
But they can't let them escape easily.
但也不能让他们轻易逃出去
Dodder Dodder
菟萝 菟萝
Someone is setting fire
有人在施火阵
The cane I held the passage was burned
我撑开通道的藤条被灼伤
Maybe not long
可能撑不久了
Feather magic
羽幻
This tomb may be collapsing
这墓室可能快塌了
go away
你们快走
I'll go first
我先去开路
you follow
你们跟着
What's wrong with Feather
羽幻 怎么了
Fire is broken
火阵被破了
they escaped
他们逃了
Send troops to chase
派兵去追啊
hold on
再等等
Your Highness is here
殿下在这儿
Su G will not come
苏摹不会不来
The seal of Liuhe is with you, right?
六合封印在你这儿吧
what their emperor can perceive
他们的皇天可以感知到的
you want to use me as bait
你想拿我做诱饵
Now we can only fight
如今只能全力一战
I try my best to keep you safe
我尽力保你周全
from beads
离珠
Take them down this road
带他们从这条路下山
etc
等等
We haven't found any water droplets yet
我们还没有找到辟水珠呢
Did you go to Queen Baiwei's tomb?
白薇王后的衣冠冢你们去了吗
went
去了
but not found
可是没找到
dodder girl
菟萝姑娘
Do you know where the water droplets are?
你可知道辟水珠在什么地方
what are you looking for
你们找它做什么
We only got the water drop
我们只有拿到了辟水珠
Only then can Su G take Na Sheng to Guishenyuan
苏摹才可以带那笙去鬼神渊
Unravel the Six Seals
解开六合封印
Are they telling the truth?
他们说得是真的吗
water droplets
辟水珠
is no longer in the tomb
已经不在衣冠冢里了
where is that
那在什么地方
Dodder, are you alright?
菟萝 你还好吧
What's going on with these leaves?
这 这些叶子怎么回事啊
Dodder girl, what's the matter with you?
菟萝姑娘 你这是怎么了
I heal you
我替你疗伤
No
不用了
Useless
没有用
hurry up
你们快点走吧
This is the last thing I can do for you
这是我能为你们做的最后的事了
To save us
为了救我们出来
You paid such a high price
你竟然付出如此大的代价
dodder girl
菟萝姑娘
Such kindness
此等恩情
Kong Sang is unforgettable
空桑 没齿难忘
you are softer than him
你比他温柔多了
Dodder girl this from the beginning
菟萝姑娘 这从一开始
It's like you know me
你就好像 认识我一样
seven thousand years ago
七千年前
I fell in love with a boy from an exotic land
我喜欢上了一个来自异域的少年
because of him
因为他
I have committed an unforgivable sin
我犯下了不可饶恕的罪过
I don't know if it's fate or what
不知是宿命还是什么
let me meet you again
让我又遇见了你
Kong Sang's Prince
空桑的太子
You have a different look from him
你跟他有着不一样的眼神
I hope you have a different ending
我希望你能有不一样的结局
The six-height seal to be unlocked
待解开六合封印
Please unlock this Jiuyi barrier
请解开这九屹结界
Let the light through the foggy forest
让光可以透过迷雾森林
So kids can turn into clouds
这样孩子们就能化成云
With the wind flowing to the blue sea
随着风流到碧落海了
don't worry
好 你放心吧
This is
这是
This is water droplets
这是辟水珠
I rely on it to absorb weak water
我靠着它吸取弱水
Survive in Jiuyi Forest
存活于九屹森林
The water pearl is originally the thing of the emperor of the sea
辟水珠本是海皇之物
It was given to Bai Wei seven thousand years ago
七千年前送给了白薇
Bai Wei was kept in the tomb after her death
白薇死后存于衣冠冢
I stole it
是我将它盗走
I just don't want it to stay with Bai Wei
就是不想它和白薇待在一起
now
如今
It's time to return the emperor
是时候归还海皇了
Chun Huang gave it to Queen Bai Wei
纯煌 送给白薇王后的
Dodder, what happened to your body
菟萝 你的身体怎么了
Dodder
菟萝
so kind
如此大恩
I must remember
我一定铭记
A new generation of Neptune
新一代的海皇
I can only protect you here
我只能保护你们到这儿了
Please be sure to defeat Cang Liu
请您务必打败沧流
With the people of Quanxian
带着泉先的子民
Back to our hometown Biluohai
回到我们的家乡碧落海
dodder, what's wrong with you
菟 菟萝 你怎么了
I was already dead
我本来早已死了
Only by this Jiuyi Mountain and Weak Shui
只是被这九屹山和弱水
stuck here
困在这里
Trapped in this sac and can't be freed
困在这皮囊里不得解脱
Now I finally got what I wanted
现在 我总算得偿所愿
finally die
总算可以死去
take the kids away
把孩子们带走
Turn them into clouds
让她们化作云雨
rise to the sky
升到这天空
Sprinkle back to the blue sea
洒落回碧落海
Ya burn this is my name
雅燃 这是我的名字
Please remember Neptune
请海皇记住
Ya burning
雅燃
Quan Xian's Heroic Soul Record
泉先的英魂录上
must have your name
一定会有你的名字
go away
你们快走吧
I will definitely fulfill your wish
我一定会完成你的心愿
to avenge you
替你报仇的
A new generation of Neptune
新一代的海皇
you have a soft heart
你有一颗柔软的心啊
Usually no one comes
后山一般没有人来
should be safe
应该安全了
sit down
坐下吧
good
好
Nasheng
那笙
The water droplets will be handed over to you
辟水珠就交给你了
I will cherish it
我会好好珍惜它的
this kindness
此恩情
On behalf of Kong Sang, I thank Quan Xian
我代表空桑谢过泉先
Only to overthrow those who are
只有推翻那些沧流人
It's not worth losing so many people
才不枉失去这么多人
Yes
是啊
The most important thing now is to find the seal
眼下最要紧的是要找到封印
Nasheng
那笙
See if the emperor reacts
你看看皇天有没有反应
seems to be over there
好像在那边
It's Qingchen
就是青辰那里
he
他
how did he go
他怎么自己去了
I gonna go see
我去看看